This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Golden Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy was sent flying from the Sabaody Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring through the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom inhabited entirely by women, Amazon Lily.
After a difficult battle, he won the favor of their empress,
a woman named Boa Hancock.
She agreed to take him back to Sabaody on a pirate ship scheduled to leave the next day.
bombust!
cameras
Ren'inion, its' terrible!
Inishida!
what's all the fuss about?!
It's awful.
She's come down with the sickness.
And no one knows what it is.
You're a damned fool, Boa Hancock
Empress or not, one does not simply ignore a summons from the world government
The weight of your pride is going to sink your entire nation
If we don't recognize you as a warlord of the sea, your position as their ruler is meaningless
Love is a hurricane, love love Hancock
Whatever it is, fight it!
Don't give up
What's this about the snake princess falling ill?
Oh, Gran and Yon
Man, I need you to wait outside
What? But why? I'm in a hurry
I know that!
It hurts
She keeps clutching her chest
Perhaps something is wrong with her heart
I've never seen anything like it
Since her symptoms are a mystery, there's very little I can do in terms of treatment
All we know is that it's extremely painful
She won't eat a thing and she's hardly speaking either
I'll be out of here tomorrow morning
Soon we're all gonna be back together
Tomorrow morning
It's as I feared
What are you doing?
Whatever it is, Gran and Yon, you've got to stop it!
Can't you see you're hurting her with this nonsense?
Do you want to get to the bottom of this or not?
Ugh, yes, of course
That fool, I should have realized
It's a pity that the virus came at a time like this
Huh? Virus?
If you know what it is, then just tell us
I can't breathe, Gran and Yon
Am I going to die like this?
Indeed, yes
I'll say it isn't so!
If this is supposed to be a joke, we're not laughing!
It has killed us before
It took the life of our last Empress
The same fate befell the Empress before her, too
I suffered from the illness myself
But left the country before it took my life
No remedy could save me
Snake Princess, Monkey Diluffi has come to see you as well
This is hardly the time
He has a request to ask of you
Will you hear it?
What do you mean, request?
Can't you see she's suffering?
How important could it be?
Oh!
What just happened?
Show him in
Quickly
Monkey Diluffi, you are a man favored by fate
Perhaps this mountain can be moved after all
And perhaps you are the one to do it
I hear you need something?
Yeah, I sure do!
But are you okay? I heard you were sick
Never mind that
No illness can overtake me
There's a pirate on Whitebeard's crew named Ace
He's my brother and he's about to be executed
I gotta go rescue him
But I heard if we took a pirate ship, it'd be too slow
That man is your brother?
Do you mean Fire Fist, Ace?
Exactly!
So instead of going back to my friends
I need you to get on a Navy ship and take me with you!
How dare you even suggest that, you selfish beast?
You know full well the horrors our poor sister went through
And still you would drag her to that abhorrent prison?
How can you be so cruel?
This is exactly why we hate men
We very well could have killed you
But as soon as we show you mercy
Then you let it go to your head
You're lucky she doesn't turn you to stone and smash you
You want me to follow the government's orders
And go with the other warlords?
He's said enough!
Strike him down!
If that is truly your request
Then of course
I will go anywhere you like
Whoa, thanks!
I was worried!
I don't know what I would have done without your help!
She actually said yes
She wouldn't listen to reason
But she'll listen to him!
What happened to her granny?
Like the Empress before her
Our Empress succumbed to the burning flames
That are known only as love
There's a saying in the East Blue
That describes these winds of passion
Love is always a miracle!
Heavens, my heart is a flutter
I feel I might do anything Luffy asks of me
I acquiesce without a second thought
And I don't regret it
Not even the slightest
That's what they call love
Love?
Once it has a hold on your heart
It will squeeze and squeeze
Until you fall over dead
If you cannot be with the one you desire
The Empresses that came before you
All fell in love with men as well
But as they were unable to leave their kingdom
They were forced to bottle up their feelings
While they stayed
Their heartache grew and grew
Until the pain was so great
That they died from sorrow
Little did you know
That by agreeing to his request
You may have saved your own life
Although you were struck with lovesickness
If Luffy had not arrived
And requested this very thing
You would have lost your title as warlord
And led this kingdom to ruin
However, one may say
That he is just as fortunate as you
After all
Had fate not brought him to this island
The only way he could hope to enter that prison
Would be in chains
Just like his brother
Hello, Momonga
Is this Boa Hancock?
Yes, and I have decided to honor
That little request of yours after all
However, there is one condition
That must be met first
Yes?
Naturally, if you can't accept
You might as well turn your boat around and leave
All right, enough suspense then
Let me hear it
I thought he wasn't leaving the kingdom until tomorrow though
I heard there was a last minute change of plans
Now he's getting on a navy ship along with a snake princess
Hi Luffy
Hey guys, thanks for everything
This was fun
I'll come back to visit and bring my friends next time
Your pirate crew?
Yeah, I bet our chef would be totally crazy about this place
He likes girls so much it's scary
Oh, but his food is awesome
I promise
I bet he'd love to cook for you
Our musician's awesome too
He's a skeleton
A skeleton?
His name's Brooke
But watch out
Because as soon as he meets you
He's going to want to check out your panties
Our panties?
I have lots to show him
But I don't see the appeal
And we've got this little reindeer doctor named Chopper too
They're all guys
Except Nami and Robin
But it's no fun if we can't all visit
Even if men are forbidden here
I think they'll make an exception
The snake princess seems to favor you
So it's not likely that they would be sentenced to death
Well, probably not at least
And there's our empress now
Who had the audacity to place these beasts in my path?
Detestable
Beastlessly adorable obstacles
We love you, princess
If I was half the sexiest, sir
I'd spend all day in front of a mirror
She's even more striking than usual
I didn't think that was possible
My deepest apologies
I accept full responsibility
You should be more careful
Hey, looks like you're feeling all better
Hate to be rude, but we gotta hurry, snake lady
I can't look him in the eye
It's too much
That's rude, Luffy
You can't call her snake lady
It's snake princess
Don't forget it
You can simply call me Hancock if you like
You're so cute
Cool
Whatever works for you, hammock
It's, uh, Hancock
The snake princess just smiled at me
It's like a diamond
No, it's like the stars in the sky
I'm dazzled
The spark of a woman in love
It makes me long for the sweet days of my youth
Why?
Is something wrong, Granny Young?
Your face is looking rather grotesque
How dare you?
Have a safe trip, snake princess
We'll miss you, Luffy
Come back soon
Bye-bye
Would you stop that?
We're serious about you coming back
Indeed, we'll await your return with faded breath
I had no obligation to save you
This is great
I was really freaking out there
I thought you guys were gonna die
Hey, Luffy
I hope you get to see your friends soon
Thanks
Granny Neon
Huh?
I'm not worried about the snake princess reaching the prison unharmed
But how will she manage to bring Luffy with her?
Well, it will require some trickery, I can say that
The man has a 300 million berry bounty on his head
And I'm certain that the navy is eager to apprehend him after what happened on Saba-Odi
But she can't very well stow him in the cargo
You need to worry
I thought up an excellent strategy and our princess can be quite persuasive
You certainly kept us waiting, Empress
In fact, I'd almost lost hope
Can you guarantee that you'll honor the promise you made earlier?
I contacted my superiors
As long as we're quick about it, we can stop by Impel Down
To be clear, only you and your snake may board
Unless they're shackled, pirates are not welcome at the prison
Warlord or no
They'll make an exception once
But know this
They'll watch you like a hawk
You can't intimidate me
Whatever you do, please try to stay safe
Strike down all who oppose you, sister
Good luck in the battle with Whitebeard, Snake Princess
Luffy, I hope you...
I shall return soon
Guard the kingdom in my absence
Of course!
I'm glad I stuck around
I feared I might have to return to headquarters of failure
You were so adamant in your refusal when last we spoke
So you'll forgive me if I ask what happened to change your mind
Hold your tongue all you like
But it seems your stomach will still speak
Even the great pirate empress is only human
How dare you
A lady such as myself would never do something so crass
There's no one else here
Of course not
Luffy, I'm sorry
I didn't eat enough at the banquet with all those girls cheesing me around and touching me
Regardless, if we get caught here, it's all over
I'll ask for food later, I promise
Just tell your stomach to be patient
Got it
And Luffy, it's difficult to walk like this
You don't have a fever, do you?
You're quite flushed
No, everything is fine
Well, while you're here, do you think you can change back my crew members that you turned to stone?
It would be shameful to show up at Navy headquarters in this unsightly state
They are alive, aren't they?
That sneeze, it sounded like a man was...
It was me!
Achoo!
This wind is bad for your health
I may be catching a cold
Sorry, I'm trying to be quiet but your hair tickled my nose
It's alright, I don't think he's on to us
I don't know what it is yet
But you're up to something and I swear I'll get to the bottom of it
Would you care to elaborate?
Aside from the fact that you're acting highly suspicious
Your demeanor is completely different than when I met with you before
We're screwed
I assure you, I have nothing to hide in either body or mind
But if you have any doubts, then I would encourage you to search me yourself if you think you are capable
Well then, what shall it be?
What the heck do you think you're doing? He's gonna find me!
No
If you insist, there's no reason to doubt your word
But I will have to ask you to fix my crew
We can scarcely operate the ship, let alone make your little trip to impel down
Awaken
Huh? What happened?
Get ready for departure!
Yes, sir!
Right away!
We'll make a stop at impel down before we return to Marineford
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! We have word from Vice Admiral Momunga!
Huh?
Snake Princess Boa Hancock came to speak with them again
She finally agreed to our conditions
I am told that they're on their way now
It's about time
Let's just hope they're not late
That woman is quite formidable
Now we'll have six of the seven warlords with us
Hawkeye Mihawk
Bartholomew Kuma
Don Quixote Doflamingo
Gekko Moria
Marshall D. Teach
And Boa Hancock
And the seventh?
Did a little time in prison cool his head?
Perhaps he's ready to aid in our fight now
No, sir!
Just as before, he's adamantly refusing to fight
He went so far as to say he would relinquish his title as warlord
Given his disposition, I had assumed that he would be the most cooperative of the bunch
This is not the time to get hung up on principle
We need you, Team Bay
Fleet Admiral, sir!
Sir, I have an announcement
We have a small issue with the 500 pirates that Admiral Kizaru captured at Sabaori
That is to say, the staff had impelled down so they can't hold them
Send them to a labor camp
Frankly, if it doesn't have to do with Whitebeard, I just don't have time for it right now
I understand, sir, but St. Roswald is, uh...
Let the admirals handle it for once
And where the hell is Garp?
Uh, I already informed you, sir, but he left for impelled down quite some time ago
I guess I should expect that kind of behavior from that old bastard, but not before a battle
Excuse me, sir
I'm afraid we have a situation
Whitebeard's ship is advancing
I see
I assume the guard ships are on the line?
Put me through, I'd rather speak to them directly
I can't do that
Huh?
We lost contact, sir
With all 23 Navy vessels keeping tabs on Whitebeard's main ship, the Moby Dick
Given the circumstances, we can only conclude they were eliminated by the enemy
Surely not the whole fleet
There's been some worrying activity from other pirate ships in the New World as well
Without guard ships, we won't have any idea how many ships the enemy is sending or when he's sending them
I've arranged for replacements, but we're in the dark right now
We've been had
I didn't think they would act so quickly
Until new ships are in place, we're flying blind
As long as Ace is there, they may even have the audacity to strike impelled down
So be ready for anything
Yes, sir
Vice Admiral, it will be right this way
Please, be careful
Sure
You're a right mess, boy
I hate to see it
You still breathing in there?
Ace
Sent flying across the world by Kuma, the Straw Hats awaken in strange new places
Nami meets a peculiar old man on a secluded island where a unique science is studied
And Frankie finds himself in a frozen land with no cola in sight
On the next One Piece, the friend's whereabouts, the science of weather and the mechanical island
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!